Music...
On every page of my destiny
In my life and after my death
Every time in my tomorrow and every moment
Please write her to me ...
In every story and all my tales
In all true love in the world of my heart
In every part of my life
Please write her to me ...
O God! whenever please do Her, mine ...
Music...
Its existence means my presence Please let she be mine
I am thirsty ... She's the river ... She's the way of my life ...
Give me a house, a street and a city But only in her name
I'll just walk for her and stop for her
If you give me a heart, just give me her trouble.
When she is with me, laughter will echo in my house
O God! whenever please do Her, mine ...
ÝpekD Çeviri Arþivi Instagram: @ipekdceviri
You can take my share of happiness, take half my smiles...
You can take my life too But promise me ...
Her tears, sorrows, and every wound ...
I will have the right to her life, anytime, anywhere...
Now it seems to me that she will always live in me
It will never leave and will always be a part of me
O God! whenever please do Her, mine ...
On every page of my destiny
In my life and after my death
Every time in my tomorrow and every moment
Please write her to me ...
ÝpekD Çeviri Arþivi - Instagram: @ipekdceviri THANKS...